Now, the selected UV case can be automatically filled to the designated position.
Go to the UV editor window to check and click on the new UV filling tool.
In the dialogue window, the filling direction is set to the interval between the UV cases.
The filling ratio is set to the percentage of the area occupied by the UV case.
Calculate based on the UV map you have chosen.
High-select rotation will allow the UV case to rotate according to the settings.
Fix the resolution ratio.
Fix the ratio of the UV cases selected at the time of selection.
Click on the application to check the effect after filling.
You can also fill the UV case to other UV frames.
Select all UV cases of the COS version.
Change to the selected frame option.
Click on the application to fill.
Insert or export multiple virtual models in the FBX format at the same time.
It will help you better complete multi-character scene production without limiting to single character.
When you need to add additional virtual models to the scene, please confirm the download type as an addition.
Under the move option, I will set the vertical axis to move 2 meters,
so that two models can be controlled.
Open the animation editor window to check the virtual model animation.
When you add a costume to the scene,
you can also set the movement value for it to match the virtual model.
Open the simulation and record the animation to check the final result.
Through the FBX, you can choose to export all virtual models.
You can also export all virtual models or some specific virtual models.
Through the roll-up function, you can roll up the opening position of the costume in a simpler way,
such as the sleeve, the pants, and so on.
Use the edit version tool to select the outline of the 2D version.
Here, select the sleeve line.
Click on the right button to select the roll-up in the pop-up menu.
You can set the number of rolls up to three times.
You can also choose the length of each roll-up.
At least 10 mm, at most 200 mm.
To make it easier for you to check the position after rolling up,
the costume in the 3D window will appear.
Click on the application to apply the input value and roll up the costume.
Open the simulation to get the natural simulation effect.
At present, the roll-up function does not support symmetrical or continuous modification.
However, when you use this function again,
it will automatically use the data from the previous time.
If you need to make an asymmetrical effect,
you can also manually modify the value.
After clicking on the application, the roll-up window is still running.
You can choose whether to reset the roll-up position according to your needs,
and return it to the original shape of the costume.
After resetting, you can set the value according to your needs and apply the roll-up again.
Selecting the roll-up function will make you choose the roll-up
with all the roll-ups with the selected roll-up.
In this example, we have deleted the roll-up between the left sleeve part and the body.
When we select a roll-up in the 2D or 3D window,
go to the main menu and edit the roll-up with all the roll-ups.
At this time, all the roll-ups with the roll-up directly or indirectly with this roll-up
will be selected together.
Then you can move them together.
When you use the adjustment roll-up tool in the 2D window
or in the 3D window,
you can use the move tool to double-click a roll-up,
and you can also select all the roll-ups with the selected roll-up.
When you press the Shift key to do the multiple selection,
if you double-click a roll-up,
you will also select all the roll-ups with the selected roll-up.
Please note that the items of the chain, side, button, inner shape, and roll-up roll-up
cannot be selected through the option of selecting all the roll-ups with the selected roll-up.
However, by connecting the roll-up to the roll-up with the pull-up function,
you can select them all through this function.
The USD file is now supported by a unified UV coordinate.
Now when you export the USD file,
you can find and select a unified UV coordinate in the pop-up window.
After selecting this option,
you can set the pixels of the UV sticker.
Select the fill-in-primitive border,
you can extend it along the primitive border.
After completion, select Confirm.
This option is also applicable to NVIDIA Omniverse Connector,
and can be imported to Adobe Photoshop
via the Omniverse Connector Live Link.
This option is more stable than SubstancePaint.